♪ All my life i was swinging for the fence ♪
♪ I was looking for the triple ♪
♪ Never playing good defense ♪
♪ Dunning both the glitter ♪
Every heart and every hour
She
我们改成夏季营业时间了
是早上八点钟开门呃
没什么人
这粉他们是同一个作者啊
这本是我学咖啡时候的教材
后面我发现他又有新的一本家用咖啡指南所
♪ 嘟嘟哩嘟嘟哩嘟 ♪
是我虫三内可颂买的超美味
There's a couple g east crazy east
When a nood to do listwo
Three four like
So much
I do do smolly soft do here
♪ We come on ♪
Day more
♪ Say you love me ♪
I do the way some bcdeep water
Do you lier to me
♪ Say you love me ♪
♪ Really ♪
♪ You love me ♪
♪ Say you love me true ♪
丁磊你们稍坐一下吧
好了
我教你们
喂朋友来
哎呦我都做好了
稍等下
巧克力巧克力牛奶茶哦
热的热的感觉
没事
你送我不换哪个来路
♪ 伊呦 ♪
♪ 巴卡雷拉高一度一呦 ♪
♪ 咦呦那沙漠西拉姆伊诺 ♪
你现在处于34岁里面的佼佼者
咱本地的货在街上走走走
别人走
年轻这俩货奔走上去
进了门房就听见走了
再叫再见
拜拜再叫再叫
把你抓住
嗯这边有没有什么
估计昨晚了两张红黑
全是躲着之家
这都不是说大货
有人过年最喜欢用
有什么饮料手机坐好坐好
我们这个对对对
鸡斤榴莲豆子
那就是30
Gushe's on the band store
Like a logo
Here just swat about your bushdone all bet that too
♪ But when that cap cares down ♪
♪ You can't help us ste ♪
Cause i playing it
Poking like a sick of lashe's on fire
♪ Oh she's zb not that good is smoking on ♪
♪ Light up bone ups ♪
♪ His own ♪
♪ We tried to look the way ♪
We all tried to be cool
But she had a nassathick as a noman news
She asked out for a drink
♪ Just a paton ♪
♪ Those eyes ♪
♪ We always reach it for a ♪
♪ While man ♪
♪ She's so alive ♪
♪ She's on fire ♪
♪ 喔一起all di ♪
♪ Oh deer is smoking on time ♪
♪ Light of my roses of di ♪
有我这个还不错是吧
对他要是客栈
他的吧台就只这么大哦
也是在哪买的
我这手滑的外套可以装修
选上我来试一试
他店在哪里啊
I've got you in hani
♪ Hear you say you ♪
♪ Don't care boy ♪
♪ Are you a man is on fire ♪
没有see d
这体感变成防烫的啦
杨飞升级的两样都非常具有
就看预算了
现在
♪ We on fire ♪
♪ Shall time is on fire ♪
今天的下午茶
香炸棒棒鸡
有不好看吗
好漂亮
这个这个绝美
这冬瓜茶一点
你想要冬瓜茶吗
就说你这冬瓜山有点东西
第二天18123去举起手中的酒杯
♪ 今夜不能睡 ♪
♪ 忘掉我所有悲伤 ♪
♪ 只留下回味 ♪
♪ 南方有一个姑娘 ♪
♪ 可我生在北方 ♪
♪ 再见吧 ♪
♪ 我的宝贝 ♪
♪ 别为我心碎 ♪
嗯你真有